linkersweddingsolutions.com 2015-12-29

# Linkers Wedding Solutions | Wedding | Wedding Planner | Event Organizer | Indian Wedding | Wedding Sites | Wedding Planners In Delhi | Wedding Planners In Chandigarh | Indian Wedding Decorations | Wedding Planning | Chandigarh Hotel | Events Management | Event Company | Events Jobs | Event Management Courses | Wedding Planner Checklist

| 

## Privacy Policy

We are committed to protecting the privacy and confidentiality of all Personal Information that you may share as a user of linkersweddingsolutions.com and IT media thereof. We have this policy to demonstrate our good faith.

This policy does not apply to the practices of organizations that we do not own or to people that we do not employ or manage.

Personal Information will be kept confidential and will be used for our research, marketing and strategic client analysis objectives and other internal business purposes only. We do not sell or rent Personal Information except that in case you are a customer of our search services through our Media, your Personal Information shall be shared with our subscribers/advertisers and you shall be deemed to have given consent to the same. Further, the subscribers / advertisers who are listed with us may call you, based on the query or enquiry that you make with us, enquiring about any product or services of any advertiser or subscriber.

We will share Personal Information only under one or more of the following circumstances: - If we have your consent or deemed consent to do so - If we are compelled by law (including court orders) to do so

In furtherance of the confidentiality with which we treat Personal Information we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

We give you the ability to edit your account information and preferences at any time, including whether you want us to contact you about new services. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

If you are our corporate customer, it is possible that we have entered into a contract with you for non-disclosure of confidential information. This Policy shall not affect such a contract in any manner.

If you have questions or concerns about these privacy policies; please send us an email at[ info@linkersweddingsolutions.com](mailto:info@linkersweddingsolutions.com)

|   
---|---|---
